



## **Professional profile**

My career in the technology field began at the age of 12 and since then, I was involved in projects related to IoT and web development. I had the opportunity to lead and collaborate in both national and international teams, working with more than 150 people. During these experiences, I focused my efforts on developing soft skills and applying agile methodologies.

### **Experience**

#### Desarrollador Full Stack & Team Leader

Jun. 2023 - Jan. 2024 · 8 months

No Country | Labor practices

I played the role of Full Stack developer, and I was also Team Leader of other teams.

- Organize team tasks and responsibilities. Implement scalable solutions in development.
- Contribute to fluid and effective communication with backend and UX/UI teams.
- Establish follow-up meetings, ensure efficient communication.
- Complete the team control, assistance and progress form.

### Technical specialist

Oct. 2021 - Dec. 2022 · 1 year 3 months

Cibeles Service

For a year, I played the role of Technical Specialist at Cibeles Service, an appliance repair company in the province of Buenos Aires.

- Ability to work autonomously and assume responsibility for assigned projects.
- Efficiency in time management and compliance with established deadlines.
- Ability to adapt to dynamic and rapidly changing work environments.

#### Lidar Image and Video Analyst for Al

May. 2021 - Sep. 2021 · 5 months

Smart Ecosystem Philippines Inc.

I participated in an In House program, in which I gained knowledge about reading spectrograms, segmentation on frames and analysis of LiDAR sensors in 2D/3D fields.

- Ability to effectively communicate findings and conclusions derived from data analysis.
- Ability to identify patterns, trends and anomalies in data.
- Ability to quickly adapt to team dynamics and assigned roles.

### **Projects**

Buffet UNAHUR Jan. 2024 - present

National University of Hurlingham - Public utility

Buffet UNAHUR is a web application designed to improve the user experience when accessing the buffet menu of the National University of Hurlingham. With this application, users can view the menu, select their preferred products, make payment conveniently, and then receive real-time notifications about the status of their order.

Front: NextJS, TailwindCSS, Typescript

**Back:** Supabase

Database: PostgreSQL

https://github.com/thomasbarenghi/buffet-app

**LleGO! | No Country**Apr. 2023 - May. 2023

Work practices

LleGO! is a platform that connects local stores with customers and delivery people, offering an experience similar to well-known services such as Uber Eats or Rappi. Our application allows stores to publish their food and product catalog, giving customers the convenience of making purchases from the comfort of their homes. Users can browse different stores, select their preferred items and place orders with ease.

**Front:** NextJS, TailwindCSS, Typescript **Back:** NestJS, Typescript, SocketIO **Database:** PostgreSQL, MongoDB

https://github.com/thomasbarenghi/llego-delivery

## **Technologies**

- Frontend: Html, Css, Sass, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Jquery, Javascript, React, NextJS, Redux, PeerJS, Typescript, GraphQL.
- Backend: NodeJS, Express, Springboot, NestJS, SocketlO, PeerJS, Supabase.
- **Databases:** MongoDB, SQLite, PostgreSQL.
- Others: Arduino, C, Blynk, Wordpress, Figma.

# **Professional education**

- Bachelor Degree in Computer's Science. National University of Hurlingham. January 2024 present.
- Self-taught programming. 2017 present.
- Electronics Technician. E.E.S.T No. 8 of Morón. December 2021.

### **Courses and certifications**

- English Certificate B1 Intermediate. EF SET. May 2023.
- CSS Skills Certification Test. HackerRank. July 2023.
- Agile Methodologies, Scrum & User Stories. Henry. May 2023.
- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 700 hours of theoretical-practical courses. May 2023.
- Quality management. National University of La Matanza. December 2021.
- Product development. National University of La Matanza. December 2021.